quintly.com 2018-06-27

# Privacy Policy | quintly

**Last updated: May 25, 2018**

At quintly, data privacy and data security are really important to us and we want to make sure that you trust us with your information. This Privacy Policy ("Policy") describes which information we gather, how we use it, how we share it with others, how we protect it and how you can access and control it.

If you have any questions or complaints about this Policy and our data protection processes, please get in touch with us at the contact mentioned below.

**"Quintly", "we", "us", "our"** means quintly Inc and its subsidiaries quintly LLC and quintly GmbH.

**"Websites"** means any website operated by Quintly

**"Services"** means any product or other service that is operated by Quintly.

**"Visitors"** means any individual that visits our Websites, but that we can't identify yet.

**"Leads"** means any Visitor of our Websites that has provided us with identifiable information (e.g., by filling a form on a landing page).

**"Users", "Customers"** means any individual who has an account with any Quintly Services.

**"GDPR"** means the General Data Protection Regulation.

Beside these specific definitions we will use the meanings as defined in the GDPR regulation.

## Information you provide to us

### Information you provide through our Websites

In specific cases you provide data to us through our Websites. For example, you provide your contact details when you sign up for our newsletter, download a white paper from one of our landing pages, use our free statistics sections or when you fill a contact form.

### Information you provide through our Services

You provide data to us when you use our Services. For example, you provide us with information, when you sign up for an account, when you add new users, when you add notes or comments or when you use our Services on an ongoing basis as part of the general features of the Services. For some data that you provide in regards of the Services we are the data processor and you are the data controller. For this purpose we will sign a data processing agreement (DPA) with you, if needed. If you would like to sign such agreement, please get in touch with us at [dataprivacy@quintly.com](mailto:dataprivacy@quintly.com).

### Information you provide through our support channels or direct communication

Through our support channels (e.g., Helpdesk, live chat) and direct email communication you provide us with data about yourself and about the case for which you are contacting us.

### Payment information

When setting up a paid account with our Services, you provide us with payment information that allow us to charge you on a recurring basis.

## Information we collect automatically

### Cookies and other tracking technologies

Cookies are small pieces of text sent by your web browser by a website you visit. A cookie file is stored in your web browser and allows the Websites or a third-party to recognize you and make your next visit easier and the Websites more useful to you.

We use cookies and other tracking technologies in order to provide our Services, give you a better website experience and to improve our Websites and Services. In our [cookie policy](https://www.quintly.com/cookie-policy?hsLang=en) you can get more information and see the list of cookies/integrations/tags that we have implemented within our Services. This includes the use of third-party analytics services like Google Analytics, Hubspot and others.

### Information on how you use our Services

When you visit and interact with our Services we collect certain information in the background in order to optimize and improve the Services going forward. This includes for example things like device and connection information, log data, logins, page views, API calls (Application Programming Interface), usage of specific features and error logging.

## Information from other sources

### Other users of the services

Other users of our Services may provide us with data about you, when they add you as a user in order to use the Services going forward. You may also be mentioned by other users in notes and comments that were added or in support/sales conversations with our team.

### Connecting via social networks

If you use any of our Websites and Services to connect with any of your social network accounts (e.g., Facebook, Instagram, Twitter, YouTube) and therefore give us permission we get access to data about you via the social network interfaces. Such data can include your name, contact info, pages you administer and analytics numbers. When you authenticate our application with the social networks, the networks will show in a dialog what data you are sharing exactly.

### Quintly companies

We may also receive data about you from other quintly affiliates, especially quintly Inc (US), quintly LLC (US) and quintly GmbH (DE).

### Public information

In some of our processes we make use of public information that we can find about you, for example via LinkedIn or similar services where you provide your information publicly with intention.

### Other partners

We may receive information about you through other third-party partners, such as advertising and data partners we work with.

We use the personal data you provided to us only for specific purposes of the corresponding processing activities and only where we have legal bases to do so (in compliance with the GDPR article 6). Once the purpose for a processing activity is not applicable anymore, we will delete the data accordingly (for specifics please read the section on this topic below). In the following sections we list the specific areas in which we use your personal data. For even more transparency we have created a [separate list of all our processing activities](https://www.quintly.com/processing-activities?hsLang=en) including the legal bases for processing that involve visitors, leads or users/customers.

## Providing of our Websites

We use information you delivered to us in order to provide our [Websites](https://www.quintly.com/processing-activities?hsLang=en#website), including customer support, log files, rendering fonts and to operate and maintain the Websites. We also use your data in order to personalize your experience.

## Providing of our Services

We use information you gave to us in order to provide our Services, including for [account creation](https://www.quintly.com/processing-activities?hsLang=en#registration), authentication, [customer support](https://www.quintly.com/processing-activities?hsLang=en#customerSupport), [log files](https://www.quintly.com/processing-activities?hsLang=en#logFiles), [rendering fonts](https://www.quintly.com/processing-activities?hsLang=en#externalFonts) and to operate and maintain the Services. We also use your data in order to personalize your experience.

### YouTube API Services

We use the YouTube API Services in order to provide our Services to you. In general we differentiate between public and private data. We collect public YouTube data via their APIs for general analysis and benchmarking use cases. If you connect our Services with your YouTube account for private data access, we will collect the private statistics of your YouTube channels in order to provide our Services to you. We will only use this private level data for your own account with our Services and will never share it with anyone else. In addition to our normal procedure for deleting stored data, you can revoke our access to your private level data via the [Google security settings page](https://security.google.com/settings/security/permissions). By using our YouTube API Services integration, you also agree to be bound by [YouTube's Terms of Service](https://www.youtube.com/t/terms). For more details you can take a look at the [Google Privacy Policy](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy).

## Improving our Services

We want to make our Services the best in the market, that's why we use your information in order to improve our Services on an ongoing basis. For example, we track how you use and navigate through our Services and how and if you use a specific feature.

## Communicating with you about our Services

We use your contact information in order to communicate with you about our services. For example, we send you emails for confirmations, customer support, updates to the Services, technical notices and security measures.

### Contact form

When you fill a [contact form](https://www.quintly.com/processing-activities?hsLang=en#contactForms) on our Websites, we use the data to get in touch with you to resolve your case.

### Request demo

When you fill a ["request demo"](https://www.quintly.com/processing-activities?hsLang=en#requestDemo) form on our Websites, we get in touch with you in order to understand your use case and schedule and deliver a web conference in order for you to decide if our Services fulfill your needs.

### Customer support

We use your information in order to provide you with the best [customer support](https://www.quintly.com/processing-activities?hsLang=en#customerSupport). For example, when you use the chat plugin in our Websites or Services, we use the information you provided in order to resolve your case and guide you to the right resources and contacts within Quintly.

## Marketing and promoting our Services

We use your data in order to send promotional information to you that may be of specific interest to you. Our goal is to make the communicated information as meaningful as possible for you.

### Newsletter

In case you signed up for our [newsletter](https://www.quintly.com/processing-activities?hsLang=en#newsletter), we will send you regular email updates about studies, our Services and other information that is interesting in the scope of our company.

### Content downloads

When you download content through our blog or and [landing page](https://www.quintly.com/processing-activities?hsLang=en#landingPages), we ask you to provide your contact information so that we can deliver the content and send you information about further content that may be of interest to you.

### Lead quality

In order to only send you meaningful information we use your information to try to [learn more about you](https://www.quintly.com/processing-activities?hsLang=en#leadQuality) over time and therefore consider a likeliness that you would be interested in our Services.

## Cookies and other tracking technologies

We use your information in combination with cookies and tracking technologies with the goal of providing you an improved Websites and Services experience.

### Cookies

We use cookies to store information and identify you across our various web properties. For example, to identify you in our Services or to track your activity in order to improve the Websites and Services. You can find the full list of cookies in our cookie policy.

### Web analytics

We use data that we gathered through [web analytics](https://www.quintly.com/processing-activities?hsLang=en#webAnalytics) scripts that we embed in our Websites and Services. For example, we use Google Analytics and Hubspot to analyze user behavior with the goal to improve the Websites and Services.

### Remarketing

We use [remarketing](https://www.quintly.com/processing-activities?hsLang=en#remarketing) in order to promote our Services to you in a personalized way. For example, we use Google Analytics/Google Adwords to build remarketing lists and Facebook ads technology (including the [Facebook pixel](https://www.facebook.com/business/help/742478679120153) and [custom audiences](https://www.facebook.com/business/help/744354708981227)) to show you ads on other platforms and re-engage you with our Websites and Services.

## Safety and security

We use information about you to increase the safety and security of our Websites and Services. For example for verifying your account, detecting fraudulent activities and anything else that would make our Services more secure.

## Service providers and third parties

We work with third-party service providers for various tasks within our organization, including billing, marketing, customer support, analysis, accounting and others. If we transfer your personal data to a service provider in order to fulfill a task, we will make sure that the service provider only processes the data based on our instructions and by guaranteeing the same safeguards as we do. On top of that we guarantee that we have signed a data processing agreement with every service provider that makes sure that the partner is bound to the strict rules under the GDPR law. We have created a [separate list of all our subprocessors](https://www.quintly.com/subprocessors?hsLang=en), so that you can clearly see who we share your data with.

## Affiliated companies and change of ownership

We may share information about you with other quintly affiliates, including quintly Inc (US), quintly LLC (US) and quintly GmbH (DE), in order to operate the Websites and Services. Any data transfer in this regard is guaranteed to be in line with the GDPR regulation. We may also share information under this Policy in the case of any merger, sale, financing or acquisition of a part or the whole of any Quintly business. We will notify you accordingly in case this situation should arise.

## Law enforcement and compliance

We will share your information with a third-party (including law enforcement authorities) if we believe that sharing is necessary to comply with any applicable law or governmental requests.

## Non-personal information

In rare cases we may share non-personal data, such as aggregated information, with third-parties, including for reporting obligations and business/marketing purposes.

We use robust and state-of-the-art [technical and organizational measures](https://www.quintly.com/technical-organizational-measures?hsLang=en) to secure the data that we have about you. For more details you can find our separate document on technical and organizational measures here. We are reviewing our data protection processes regularly in order to make sure that we protect your data in the best possible way. If we use sub contractors and service providers to fulfill a specific task based on your data, we will make sure that the partner has similar state-of-the-art data protection processes in place.

We store your data only for as long as we need access to it in order to fulfill the purpose of the specific data processing activity. As the data retention period is different from use case to use case we have created a separate document with all our [processing activities](https://www.quintly.com/processing-activities?hsLang=en), in which you can find the exact period for each of the processing activities that we perform. On top of that and where possible we have applied a general rule inside Quintly that all personal data should be deleted or anonymized if you haven't been using our Websites and Services for more than 9 months. Exceptions to this rules only apply if there are technical limitations to guarantee this or where specific laws expect from us that we store the data for a longer time (e.g., requirements from tax authorities for storing documents).

We respect that your personal data is yours and therefore give you full control to decide what happens with your personal data.

## Access, correction and deletion

You have the right to request a copy of your information, to object to our use of it, to request the deletion of your information or to get it in a machine-readable electronic format. Many of these activities you can do yourself within our Services by navigating to the account settings page. For any other request please send us an email to [dataprivacy@quintly.com](mailto:dataprivacy@quintly.com) and we will do our best to give you a meaningful response as soon as possible after we have verified your identity. In some cases we may be limited in providing information to you, if fulfilling your request would reveal information about any other individual or if we are permitted by law or legitimate interest to keep it. Should you at any point believe that we didn't respect your data privacy rights, you can complain with the corresponding authorities.

## Opting out for specific use cases

You may opt-out of specific processing activities by using different methods, such as

  * Blocking cookies in your browser
  * Switching the settings in our cookie consent solution (Websites and Services)
  * Installing third-party browser extensions to block certain scripts (e.g., [Google Analytics](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout))
  * Clicking on unsubscribe links in marketing email that we sent

In many cases we use sub contractors, service providers and quintly affiliates that are based outside of the European Union. Should this be the case, we will always make sure that safeguards apply so that the corresponding data transfer is handled in line with the GDPR regulations. For sub processors in the US we rely on the EU/US Privacy Shield framework and signed data processing agreements that make sure that your data is secure. We have created a separate list of all processing activities that include all used sub contractors, their country of origin and the corresponding safeguards.

## Business audience

Our Websites and Services are intended to be used exclusively by organizations or by individuals in an organizational capacity.

## Minors and children

The Websites and Services are not directed to individuals under the age of 16 and we do not knowingly collect any information from individuals under 16. If we become aware of such data, we will delete the personal information. If you become aware that someone under 16 is using our Websites and Services or has provided us with personal information, please get in touch with us at the contact mentioned below.

## Changes to this policy

Quintly reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy. We will provide notification of material changes through the company's website at least 30 days prior to the change taking effect. Your continued use of the Websites and Services after the update has become effective indicates that you have read, understood and agreed to the new version of this Policy.

Questions regarding this policy or data privacy in general can be directed to the following contacts.

## Responsible for data privacy and security at quintly

quintly Inc<br> 2443 Fillmore St #380-2372<br> San Francisco, CA 94115<br> United States

quintly LLC<br> 2443 Fillmore St #380-2372<br> San Francisco, CA 94115<br> United States

quintly GmbH<br> Neusser Str. 93<br> 50670 Cologne<br> Germany

Represented by Alexander Peiniger<br> CEO and Managing Director<br> [dataprivacy@quintly.com](mailto:dataprivacy@quintly.com)

## Independent data protection officer

DSBX UG (haftungsbeschränkt)<br> Am Sandfeld 17a<br> 76149 Karlsruhe<br> Germany<br> [quintly@dsbx.one](mailto:quintly@dsbx.one)
